Father
A Lan
What's so urgent that you're looking for Father?
Nothing major.
By the way,
Why did you send Yuwen Rui to Yu Zhen?
There's a lead on the Sword Maniac in Yu Zhen.
I sent him to investigate.
What?
Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
You'll miss him?
Of course not.
I heard you've been pestering Grand Tutor Guan lately.
And even sneaking out of the palace to see him.
Your daughter noticed Grand Tutor Guan
has seemed troubled recently.
I wanted to cheer him up.
Why don't I see you trying to cheer your father up?
Your daughter actually has a big matter
to make Father happy.
Princess.
The vendor said this Beauty Powder must be dissolved in water.
Should I put it in the tea now?
Princess?
Go ahead.
Lord Yuwen will be here soon.
This servant will go prepare some snacks.
Lord Yuwen.
My lord departs the capital tomorrow.
You must have much to discuss with the princess.
I have given orders
to ensure no one disturbs you.
My lord, please go in.
The princess has specially prepared a big gift for you.
A big gift?
My Lord.
These past days,
our people have been searching everywhere for the Sword Maniac.
We finally found his trail
and seized the final key.
As you ordered,
I had people spread
the false rumor of the Sword Maniac being in Yu Zhen.
Just as you predicted,
the Yunmi emperor has ordered Yuwen Rui
to go to Yu Zhen.
Is everything arranged?
Death squad members are already positioned along the route.
They will surely ensure Yuwen Rui
never returns.
Spare his life.
Just make sure he cannot return to Luo Jing.
My Lord,
this...
What?
Are my words not effective?
This subordinate wouldn't dare.
My Lord,
the Fifth Princess has been persistently bothering Grand Tutor Guan lately.
Could she have discovered something?
If she had discovered anything,
it wouldn't be so calm.
What time do you leave tomorrow?
At Chen hour.
Aphrodisiac Powder?
This... this tea...
Does it taste strange?
You told Xixi to add something special.
You had Xixi add it?
For me to drink?
Obviously.
Aren't you drinking it right now?
I heard
you prepared a big gift.
Xixi told you?
Where's the gift?
Far away on the horizon,
yet right before your eyes.
If all goes well,
I'll be back soon.
You didn't need to prepare such a grand gift.
Of course it's necessary.
Hurry up and unwrap the gift.
Perhaps the gift should be unwrapped another day.
Why not now?
Are you sure?
I'm sure.
No regrets?
What's there to regret about this?
Fine.
As you wish.
What are you doing?
Unwrapping the gift.
Yuwen Rui, you're acting strange.
You're the one acting strange.
Me?
What's wrong with you?
You put Aphrodisiac Powder in the tea.
And you ask what's wrong with me?
Aphrodisiac Powder?
Wasn't that Beauty Powder?
The free sample must have been mixed up.
Are you okay?
What do you think?
In cheesy TV dramas,
the aphrodisiac plot is always there.
What do we do now?
Calm down first.
How am I supposed to calm down?
It really is red.
What are you doing?
Put me down!
Where's the wound medicine?
You don't actually think
I wanted to do something to you, do you?
I don't want you to feel
you aren't cherished.
If this were a TV show,
the comments would only question you.
It's nothing.
The wound medicine.
It's fine.
Just a minor bump.
Get some rest early.
It's quite late.
You have to travel early tomorrow.
Stay and rest here tonight.
Once everything is settled,
I will request permission for us to marry soon.
There's no hurry.
Things are fine as they are now.
What do you mean no hurry?
I've been waiting all this time.
Sleep.
This is a protective talisman I made for you myself.
Wait for me to return.
Stop being so lovey-dovey.
Yu Zhen isn't far.
Big brother will be back in five days at most.
By the way, big brother,
A Zi is busy with the Celestial Rite preparations.
She asked me to pass on a message.
She wishes you a safe journey.
I'll take a detour via Qi Zhen to Yu Zhen.
It might delay me by two days.
Take care of yourself.
I'm afraid it's a one-way trip.
I came to see A Lan.
I'm definitely not here to see you.
I know.
You came to find the Fifth Princess
and just happened to see me.
From now on,
I...
I... can I call you Yinglu?
Yinglu.
Can I...
give you a hug?
Yinglu.
A Lan.
What have you been up to since you got back?
You didn't even come find me.
I missed you so much!
I missed you too.
There's been so much going on lately.
But,
it seems like you've
been busy with other things too.
Why is Commander He here too?
You two...
We...
ran into each other
by coincidence.
Fifth Princess,
this humble official will take his leave.
Commander He,
wait.
There's something I want to ask you.
Commander He,
do you have a woman you like?
No.
That's great!
The legitimate daughter of the Xia Residence
told me just yesterday
that she admires Commander He
and will marry no one but him.
Miss Xia has exceptional grace
and is gentle and lovely.
Commander He isn't getting any younger either.
How about I play matchmaker?
This humble official... I am of lowly status and scant fortune.
How could I possibly...
What's all this "lowly status and scant fortune"?
Commander He is young
and already the Commander of the Imperial Guard.
No wonder Miss Xia
insists on marrying you.
Alright then,
I'll go find Father right now
to arrange your marriage.
How about that?
A Lan!
What?
I...
I understand.
Yinglu has reached marriageable age too.
Oh!
Let me tell you,
this Miss Xia has an older brother
who is also an outstanding man.
If you're willing,
Commander He might one day
have to call you "sister-in-law."
Who wants to be his sister-in-law?!
Don't get so worked up.
I...
Alright, alright.
I get it.
Then I'll help you
look for other men.
Commander He,
Miss Xia is truly as beautiful as a fairy.
I guarantee once you see her,
you'll fall for her at first sight.
Fifth Princess,
actually, this humble official already has someone he likes.
Don't lie.
You just said you didn't.
Don't be shy.
Let's go.
The person he likes is me.
Commander He,
you're welcome.
A Lan!
You actually tricked me!
You lied to me first.
How dare you criticize me?
When did you and Lord Yuwen
get together?
Do you know
my brother, he...
What about your brother?
It's nothing.
Hurry up and tell me
about your trip south.
Well, that's a long story.
Seventh Cousin.
What is it?
Nothing.
I haven't seen you at the palace these past few days.
I saw you were busy with the Celestial Rite,
so I didn't disturb you.
After the Celestial Rite,
I will speak to Father about us.
How about that?
What's wrong?
Nothing.
His Majesty
probably won't agree to our marriage.
If Father doesn't agree,
I'll find a way to make him agree.
As long as our hearts are as one,
everything else
is unimportant.
Really?
Of course.
A Zi,
come with me.
my mother told me
even without parental consent
or a matchmaker's words,
as long as two people truly love each other,
they can still receive heaven's blessing.
A Zi,
would you be willing to take heaven and earth as witness,
the sun and moon as our guide,
and become husband and wife with me?
Why not?
First bow to heaven and earth.
Second bow to the parents.
Husband and wife bow to each other.
From now on,
you are my wife.
One final step.
I read in a storybook that
newlyweds
bury their wedlock hair under intertwined branches
to be blessed to stay together in life and death.
A harmonious union for a hundred years.
You read it in a storybook.
How can you believe that?
Better to believe it's true
than to believe it's false.
This should do it.
I wish time could just stop at this moment.
Don't worry.
Things will be better in the future.
Zixiu sent you.
Lord Grand Secretary is indeed brilliant.
At least I'll die knowing the truth today.
Attack!
Lord Grand Secretary is truly formidable.
But no matter how skilled you are,
you can't save the Fifth Princess now.
Bring her up.
A Lan.
A Lan!
Why do I suddenly feel so uneasy?
I'm sorry.
My Lord.
Yuwen Rui is dead.
Didn't you say to spare his life?
Perhaps the situation was too critical.
They couldn't afford to hold back.
My Lord.
Yuwen Rui is dead.
It's all gain and no loss for us.
Tomorrow's affairs are all arranged.
Rest assured, My Lord.
Everything will proceed as planned.
As for the Fourth Princess of Yunmi,
how does My Lord intend to handle her?
Post guards to watch her closely.
Without orders,
she is not to leave her chambers.
For tomorrow's Celestial Rite,
announce that she has caught a chill.
She is not fit to go out.
Understood.
Take good care of her.
Do not make things difficult for her.
Yes.
Where are A Lan and A Zi?
Why haven't they arrived yet?
Your Majesty,
word from the Fourth Princess's quarters is
she suddenly fell ill with a chill today.
She is not fit to attend.
As for the Fifth Princess,
A Lan has always been fond of play.
It's not the first time she's been late.
Princess.
I've made inquiries.
Grand Tutor Guan has been staying at his residence these past few days.
Nothing out of the ordinary.
He entered the palace this morning
to make final preparations for the Celestial Rite.
Princess.
You must hurry.
The Celestial Rite has already begun.
All the masters in the palace, except you and the Fourth Princess,
have already gone over.
My elder sister hasn't gone either?
The Fourth Princess has caught a chill.
I'm afraid she won't be going today.
How did she catch a chill out of the blue?
I know about this matter.
This morning, I ran into Xiao Liangzi.
Xiao Liangzi said
he secretly saw
the Fourth Princess and Young Master Xiu
under the peach blossoms in Jingfeng Forest,
pledging themselves to each other.
Young Master Xiu also buried their wedlock hair
under the tree.
The wind was strong.
Perhaps that's why the Fourth Princess
caught a chill.
Seventh Cousin is quite romantic.
Nanny.
This is delicious.
Try some.
What is it, Princess?
Nanny.
What is this tune called?
How do you...
Princess.
The nanny was originally from Yunze.
She hums this tune from time to time.
It might be an old Yunze melody.
A Yunze melody...
Tell me.
Who is this despairing old man?
You know him.
Grand Tutor Guan.
He will, inside the Benevolent Heart Hall,
dash himself against the imperial desk and die.
Grand Tutor Guan...
The Celestial Rite...
What did you just say?
I... I just said
Grand Tutor Guan has been normal these past few days.
No.
After that.
Further back.
I said
I ran into Xiao Liangzi this morning.
Further back.
The Fourth Princess and Young Master Xiu
pledged themselves to each other.
Young Master Xiu also buried their wedlock hair
under the tree.
In my homeland,
on the day a couple marries,
they take strands of their hair
and bury them together under intertwined branches
to pray for a long life together.
Seventh Cousin...
Princess, what's wrong?
During the Celestial Rite,
isn't Grand Tutor Guan supposed to present
the Heavenly Water to Father?
Yes.
Every year at the Celestial Rite,
three cups of wine are prepared.
One is offered to heaven and earth.
One is offered to the ancestors.
And the last cup
is presented to His Majesty by a venerable elder
to pray for favorable weather
and peace for our Yunmi.
For national prosperity and people's safety.
Princess?
Princess!
Where are you going?
Your Majesty!
Father, don't drink it!
What...